Office of the Vice President for Business and Finance records, 1950-ongoing UA.10.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 78-129.
  - Architect, University, J. Ward, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Army Research Office -- Durham (AROD), 1968-1970 (Box 14)
  - Art Dept., 1967-1974 (Box 14)
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1968-1976 (Box 14)
  - Association for Academic Health Centers (AAHC), 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Banks, 1963-1965 (Box 14)
  - Botany, Dept. of, 1967-1974 (Box 14)
  - Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
  - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Budget -- Business and Finance Div., FY 1973-1974, FY 1974-1975 (Box 14)
  - Budget -- Business and Finance Div., FY 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Budget -- Departmental, FY 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - Budget -- Departmental, FY 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Budget Committee, University, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Budgets and Measurements (H. Brooke, Mgr.], 1974-1975 (Box 15)
  - Budgets and Measurements (H. Brooke, Mgr.], 1976 (Box 15)
  - Building and Grounds Committee -- Correspondence, Memos, 1966-1970 (Box 15)
    Building and Grounds Committee materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Building and Grounds Committee -- Correspondence, Memos, 1971-1976 (Box 15)
  - Building and Grounds Committee -- Minutes, Reports, 1966-1971 (Box 15)
  - Building and Grounds Committee -- Minutes, Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 15)
  - Business Administration, Graduate School of, 1967-1976 (Box 15)
  - Business Auxiliaries, 1972-1975 (Box 15)
  - Business Auxiliaries, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Business and Finance Advisory Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 15)
  - Business and Finance Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 15)
    Business and Finance Committee materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Business and Finance Division, 1967-1977 (Box 15)
  - Business and Finance Division -- Annual Conference, 1967-1976 (Box 15)
  - Business and Finance Division -- Progress Reports, 1968-1970 (Box 15)
  - Business and Finance Division -- Space Needs, 1970-1972 (Box 15)
  - Business and Finance Report (Newsletter), 1976 (Box 15)
  - Business Manager, 1971-1972 (Box 15)
  - Business Manager, 1973 (Box 15)
  - Business Manager, 1974, 1976 (Box 15)
  - Campus Services [Pietrantoni, Dir.], 1976 (Box 16)
  - Central Carolina Bank (CCB), 1969-1974 (Box 16)
  - Chancellor [K. Pye], 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Chancellor (Blackburn], 1974-1975 (Box 16)
  - Chancellor (K. Pye], 1976 (Box 16)
  - Chapel, 1967-1976 (Box 16)
  - Chemistry Dept., 1966-1976 (Box 16)
  - Committees, University -- Misc., 1970-1975 (Box 16)
  - Committee for Economic Development (CED) -- Report on Federal Aid to Higher Ed., 1972 (Box 16)
  - Commonwealth Studies, Center for, 1968-1970, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Community Relations, University [Bubas, V.P], 1971-1976 (Box 16)
  - Computing, University, 1975 (Box 16)
  - Computing, University, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Conflict of Interest Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 16)
  - Consortium on Financing Higher Education, 1975-1976 (Box 16)
  - Contracts -- Misc., 1967-1975 (Box 16)
  - Controller [P. Fuller], 1970-1974 (Box 16)
  - Controller [P. Fuller], 1975 (Box 16)
  - Controller [P. Fuller], 1976 (Box 16)
  - Controller, Deputy [Adcock], 1976 (Box 16)
  - Dean of Faculty [H. Lewis], 1967-1965 (Box 16)
  - Dining Halls, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Divinity School, 1967-1974 (Box 16)
  - Duke Endowment, 1970-1971 (Box 16)
  - Duke Endowment, 1972 (Box 16)
  - Duke Endowment, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Duke Endowment, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Duke Endowment, 1975, [2 folders] (Box 17)
  - Duke Endowment, 1976, [2 folders] (Box 17)
  - Duke Forest, 1968-1975 (Box 17)
  - Duke Marine Lab, 1972-1974 (Box 17)
  - Duke Marine Lab, 1975-1976 (Box 17)
  - Duke Power Co., 1972-1976 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Athletic Association (DUAA), 1971-1974 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Athletic Association (DUAA), 1975 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Athletic Association (DUAA), 1976 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Athletic Association (DUAA) -- Special Report, 1971 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Athletic Association (DUAA) -- Long Range Plans, 1973-1978 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Environmental Concerns Committee (DUECC), 1970-1972 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Environmental Concerns Committee (DUECC), 1973 (Box 17)
  - Duke University Environmental Concerns Committee (DUECC), 1974-1976 (Box 17)
  - Durham Urban Observatory, 1974-1976 (Box 17)
  - East Campus -- Summer Use, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Eastern Association of College and University Business Officers (EACUBO), 1968-1974 (Box 18)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1966-1970 (Box 18)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1971-1976 (Box 18)
  - Electrical Substation, 44KV, 1967 (Box 18)
  - Electrical Substation, 44KV, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
  - Electrical Substation, 44KV, 1970-1972 (Box 18)
  - Energy Conservation, 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - Engineering, School of, 1966-1968 (Box 18)
  - Engineering, School of, 1969-1976 (Box 18)
  - Epoch Campaign, 1973-1976 (Box 18)
  - Equal Employment Opportunities, 1966-1972 (Box 18)
  - Equal Employment Opportunities, 1973-1975 (Box 18)
  - Equal Employment Opportunities, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Ewing, Maurice -- Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 18)
  - Fallout Preparedness Committee, 1963 (Box 18)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Fine Arts Subcommittee (of the University Planning Committee), 1971-1972 (Box 18)
  - Forestry, School of, 1967-1976 (Box 18)
  - Fringe Benefits, 1971-1974 (Box 18)
  - Fringe Benefits, 1975-1976 (Box 18)
  - Handicapped Regulations, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Highland Hospital, 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Homesites, Duke Faculty, 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - Housing Management, 1970-1971 (Box 19)
  - Housing Management, 1972-1973 (Box 19)
  - Housing Management, 1974-1976 (Box 19)
  - Howard, W. K, 1973-1974 (Box 19)
  - Howard, W. K., 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Institutional Advancement (Office of Development), 1968-1971 (Box 19)
  - Institutional Advancement (Office of Development), 1972-1974 (Box 19)
  - Institutional Advancement (Office of Development), 1975-1976 (Box 19)
  - Insurance, 1974-1975 (Box 19)
  - Internal Audit Office, 1971-1973 (Box 19)
  - Internal Audit Office, 1974-1975 (Box 19)
  - Internal Audit Office, 1976 (Box 19)
  - Interstate 40 (I-40), 1970-1974 (Box 19)
  - Investment Committee, Duke University, 1967-1972 (Box 19)
    RESTRICTED
  - Investment Committee, Duke University, 1973 (Box 19)
    Investment Committee materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Investment Committee, Duke University, 1974 (Box 19)
  - Investment Committee, Duke University, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Investment Committee, Duke University, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Kearns, Amos -- Correspondence, 1969-1976 (Box 20)
  - Law School, 1967-1976 (Box 20)
  - Libraries, 1967-1976 (Box 20)
  - Materials Support Dept., 1976 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Budget -- Duke Hospital, 1968-1971, 1975-1976 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Budget -- Misc, 1974-1976 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Budget -- Physical Plant, FY 1975-1976 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Budget -- School of Medicine, FY 1975-1976 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Business and Finance (Steinert, VP], 1969-1971 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Business and Finance (Steinert, Asst. VP, Health Affairs], 1972-1975 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Contracts (with VA Hospital], 1969-1972 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital -- Financial Information, 1969-1976 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital -- Misc. Reports, 1970-1976 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital -- Office of the Director (Sessoms), 1967-1972 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center --Duke Hospital -- Office of the Director, 1974-1975 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1970-1974 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1974 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1975 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1976 (Box 20)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Eye Center, 1971-1975 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Health Affairs (Anlyan, VP), 1969-1971 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Health Affairs, 1972-1973 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Health Affairs, 1974 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Health Affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Health Affairs -- Administration (Shytle, VP), 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center -- Health Affairs -- Planning and Analysis (Elchlepp, VP), 1974-1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Main Entrance Building Construction, 1966-1969 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Management Engineering Steering Committee, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Management Engineering Steering Committee, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Misc. Correspondence and Reports, 1967-1971 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Misc. Correspondence and Reports, 1972-1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Parking, 1969-1975 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Planning Office (Swanson, Dir.], 1970-1975 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Private Diagnostic Clinic (PDC), 1966-1972 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Private Diagnostic Clinic (PDC), 1973-1974 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Private Diagnostic Clinic (PDC), 1975-1976 (Box 21)
  - Medical Center --- Vice Provost (B. Woodhall], 1966-1970 (Box 21)
  - Medicine, School of, 1970-1976 (Box 21)
  - Nanaline H. Duke Fund, 1968 (Box 22)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO), 1968-1974 (Box 22)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO), 1975-1976 (Box 22)
  - National Geographic (A. Brown, Asst. Ed.), 1976 (Box 22)
  - Nello L. Teer Co., 1967-1976 (Box 22)
  - New Hop Creek, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
  - Nuclear Lab, 1967-1970 (Box 22)
  - Nursing, School of, 1968-1976 (Box 22)
  - Organization of Tropical Studies (OTS), 1971-1973 (Box 22)
  - Organizational Planning, 1971-1973 (Box 22)
  - Overhead Rates, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
  - Paths for Employee Progress (PEP), 1969-1976 (Box 22)
  - Payroll Statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 22)
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co (PMM), 1974-1976 (Box 22)
  - Personnel (R. L. Jackson, Asst. VP), 1974-1976 (Box 22)
  - Personnel (R. L. Jackson, Asst VP), 1976 (Box 22)
  - Personnel -- Employee Relations Office (H. Aikens, Dir.), 1974-1976 (Box 22)
  - Personnel -- Labor Relations (Maginnes, Dir.), 1975 (Box 22)
  - Personnel -- Wage and Salary Administration, 1974-1976 (Box 22)
  - Personnel -- Wage and Salary Administration, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Personnel Policy Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 22)
  - Personnel Policy Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 22)
  - Personnel Policy Committee, 1976 (Box 22)
  - Personnel Policy Committee -- Drafts, n.d. (Box 22)
  - Physical Education Dept., 1969-1971 (Box 22)
  - Physical Education Dept., 1972-1974 (Box 22)
  - Physical Education Dept., 1975-1976 (Box 22)
  - Physical Facilities Subcommittee (of the University Planning Committee) -- Minutes, Reports, Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 23)
  - Physical Facilities Subcommittee (of the University Planning Committee) -- Draft Resolutions, Reports, 1972 (Box 23)
  - Physical Plant Dept., 1973 (Box 23)
  - Physical Plant Dept., 1974 (Box 23)
  - Physical Plant Dept., 1975 (Box 23)
  - Physical Plant Dept., 1976 (Box 23)
  - Policies and Procedures (Judicial), 1968-1970 (Box 23)
  - Policies and Procedures, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - President Terry Sanford, 1969-1972 (Box 23)
  - President Terry Sanford, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - President Terry Sanford, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - President's Council on Black Affairs, 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - President's Council on Government Relations, 1976 (Box 23)
  - Provost (F. Cleveland), 1973-1976 (Box 23)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 1967-1976 (Box 23)
  - Public Relations, 1967-1976 (Box 23)
  - Public Safety Dept., (P. Dumas), 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Raleigh-Durham Airport (RDU), 1974 (Box 23)
  - Raleigh-Durham Airport (RDU), 1975-1976 (Box 23)
  - Rauch, Henry -- Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 23)
  - Real Estate, 1974-1976 (Box 23)
  - Rings (Class), 1970 (Box 23)
  - Regional Program (E. Hopkins, VP), 1966-1971 (Box 23)
  - Registrar, University, 1967-1976 (Box 23)
  - Renovations -- East Campus Recreational Facility, 1967-1974 (Box 24)
  - Renovations --- Electrical Power System (44 KV), 1968-1974 see also Electrical Substation (Box 24)
  - Renovations --- Intramural Building, 1971-1972 (Box 24)
  - Renovations --- Medical Sciences (I-B and I-C), 1971-1972 (Box 24)
  - Renovations --- Memorial Gym (East Campus), 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Renovations -- Mental Retardation and Child Development Civitan Facility, 1967-1970 (Box 24)
  - Renovations -- Misc., 1968-1970 (Box 24)
  - Renovations -- Music Building, 1969-1976 (Box 24)
  - Renovations -- Post Office, 1966-1975 (Box 24)
  - Renovations -- Primate Center, 1966-1975 (Box 24)
  - Renovations -- Swimming Pool, 1967-1974 (Box 24)
  - Renovations -- University Union, 1970-1976 (Box 24)
  - Research Triangle Foundation, 1967, 1971-1973 (Box 24)
  - Research Triangle Foundation, 1974 (Box 24)
  - Research Triangle Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box 24)
  - Research Triangle Institute (RTI), 1969 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Research Triangle Institute (RTI), 1975 (Box 24)
  - Research Triangle Institute (RTI), 1976 (Box 24)
  - Residential Life Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 24)
  - Residential Life Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 24)
  - Residential Life Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Retirement, 1968-1971 (Box 24)
  - Retirement, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Retirement, 1974-1976 (Box 24)
  - Rock Climbing, 1972-1973 (Box 24)
  - Safety, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
  - Safety, 1974 (Box 25)
  - Safety, 1975-1976 (Box 25)
  - Salaries, 1962-1974 (Box 25)
    Salaries materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Secretary, University (R. Powell), 1974-1976 (Box 25)
  - Seeley Mudd Fund, 1971-1976 (Box 25)
  - Special Projects (G. Kantner), 1967-1969 (Box 25)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1967-1971 (Box 25)
  - Sponsored Programs, 1972-1976 (Box 25)
  - Student Affairs (Griffith, Dean), 1974-1975 (Box 25)
  - Student Affairs (Griffith, Dean), 1976 (Box 25)
  - Student Health, 1973-1976 (Box 25)
  - Student Loans, 1969-1976 (Box 25)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, 1973 (Box 25)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, 1974 (Box 25)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, Jan-March, 1975 (Box 25)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, April-May, 1975 (Box 25)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, June-Aug, 1975 (Box 25)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, Oct-Dec, 1975 (Box 25)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, Jan-March, 1976 (Box 26)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, April-May, 1976 (Box 26)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, July-Sept, 1976 (Box 26)
  - T. Rowe Price -- Reports, Oct-Dec, 1976 (Box 26)
  - Telephone, 1968-1970 (Box 26)
  - Telephone, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Telephone, 1972 (including TelCom) (Box 26)
  - Telephone, 1973 (including TelCom) (Box 26)
  - Telephone, 1973 (including TelCom) (Box 26)
  - Telephone, 1974 (Box 26)
  - Telephone, 1975-1976 (Box 26)
  - Track Meet: USSR-USA, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
  - Track Meet: USA -- PanAfrica -- W. Germany, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Traffic Commission, 1974-1976 (Box 26)
  - Transportation and Safety, Dept. of (NCDOT), 1974-1975 (Box 26)
  - Treasurer (S. C. Harward), 1969-1975 (Box 26)
  - Triangle Universities Computation Center (TUCC), 1974-1975 (Box 26)
  - Troika, 1969, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Trustees -- Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 26)
  - Tuition, 1963-1975 (Box 26)
  - Unions -- Local 465 (Operating Engineers), 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Unions -- Local 465 (Operating Engineers), 1974-1976 (Box 26)
  - Unions -- Local 77, 1971-1973 (Box 26)
  - Unions -- Local 77, 1974-1975 (Box 26)
  - University Counsel (K. Pye), 1971-1974 (Box 27)
  - University Counsel (C.L. Haslam), 1974-1975 (Box 27)
  - University Counsel (C.L. Haslam), 1976 (Box 27)
  - University House, 1969-1974 (Box 27)
  - University Planning Commission (UPC), 1972-1974 (Box 27)
  - University Union, 1966-1975 (Box 27)
  - Vanderbilt-Duke (Comparative Studies), 1968-1972 (Box 27)
  - Veterinary Medicine, Dept. of, 1967 (Box 27)
  - WDBS -- Bylaws, 1970-1974 (Box 27)
  - WDBS -- Correspondence and Misc., 1970-1974 (Box 27)
  - WDBS -- Correspondence and Misc., 1975-1976 (Box 27)
  - WDBS -- Financial Information, 1970-1973 (Box 27)
  - WDBS -- Financial Information, 1974-1976 (Box 27)
  - WDBS -- General Managers Reports, 1971-1975 (Box 27)
  - WDBS -- Minutes -- Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1970-1976 (Box 27)
  - WDBS -- Minutes -- Managerial Board and Staff Meetings, 1971-1975 (Box 27)
  - Whitehead Medical Research Institute, 1976 (Box 27)
  - Woman's College, 1967-1968 (Box 27)
  - Woman's College, 1969-1970 (Box 27)
  - Woodlands and Whitewater Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 27)
  - Board of Trustees Executive Committee Meetings (Box 28)
    All Board of Trustees materials are RESTRICTED.
    - October 7, 1966 - November 7, 1969 (Box 28)
    - December 12, 1969 - July 19, 1971 (Box 29)
    - August 27, 1971 - March 1, 1974 (Box 30)
    - April 5, 1974 - December 10-11, 1976 (Box 31)
- Accession 81-81.
  Contains Huestis' subject files from 1967-1980 (bulk 1976-1979). Consists largely of financial information and correspondence concerning the Medical Center, Personnel Department materials, and folders on various renovation projects underway in the mid- to late- 1970s. The remainder of this series is primarily subject files on university committees, organizations, and departments.
  - Academic Council, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Accounting, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1977 (Box 32)
  - American Dance Festival (ADF), 1977 (Box 32)
  - Architect, University (Ward), 1977 (Box 32)
  - Art Dept., 1977 (Box 32)
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1977 (Box 32)
  - Association for Academic Health Centers (AAHC), 1977 (Box 32)
  - (Duke University) Athletic Association, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Audit, Internal, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, Feb. 25-26, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, May 6-7, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, Sept. 23-24, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Board of Trustees -- Meeting, Dec. 9-10, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Board of Trustees -- Correspondence, 1977 (Box 32)
  - Booz, Allen and Hamilton, 1970-1976 (Box 32)
  - Budget, FY 75/76 (Box 32)
  - Budget, FY 76/77 (Box 32)
  - Budget, FY 77-78 (Box 32)
  - Budgets and Measurements, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Building and Grounds Committee, 1977 (Box 33)
    Buildings and Grounds Committee materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Business Auxiliaries, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Business and Finance Advisory Committee, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Business and Finance Committee, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Business and Finance Committee -- Operations Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 33)
  - Business and Finance Committee -- Operations Reports, FY 76/77-FY 78/79 (Box 33)
  - Business and Finance Newsletter, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Business Manager (J. Henderson), 1977 (Box 33)
  - Campus Services, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Chancellor (K. Pye), 1977 (Box 33)
  - Chapel, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Computing, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Corporate Controller (J.P. Fuller), 1977 (Box 33)
  - Controller, University (Adcock), 1977-1979 (Box 33)
  - Credit Union, 1967- 1977 (Box 33)
  - Dining Halls, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Divinity School, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Duke Endowment, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Duke Forest, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Duke Power Co., 1977 (Box 33)
  - Duke Marine Lab, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Economics, Dept. of, 1970- 1977 (Box 33)
  - Education, Dept. of, 1970- 1977 (Box 33)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Energy Conservation, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Engineering, Dept. of, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Environmental Concerns Committee, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Epoch Campaign, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity, 1977 (Box 33)
  - Executive Committee (of the Board of Trustees), 1977 (Box 33)
    Executive Committee materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Executive Jet Aviation, 1975 (Box 33)
  - Faculty Club, 1970-1977 (Box 34)
  - Financial Aid, 1976-1976 (Box 34)
  - Fringe Benefits, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Fuller, Vivian vs. Duke Univ., 1976 RESTRICTED (Box 34)
  - Geology, Dept. of, 1967-1976 (Box 34)
  - Gifts and Grants, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Gothic Services, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Handicapped Regulations, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Health, Education & Welfare, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Highland Hospital, 1976 (Box 34)
  - History Dept., 1967-1976 (Box 34)
  - Homesites, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Housing (Smith and Adams), 1976 (Box 34)
  - Institutional Advancement & Development, 1976 (Box 34)
  - Internal Development Committee, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Investment Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 34)
  - Investment Opportunities, 1977 (Box 34)
  - (Fletcher R.) Jones Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box 34)
  - Kidder-Peabody and Co., Inc. (Box 34)
  - Kreps, Juanita (U.S. Secretary of Commerce), 1977 (Box 34)
  - Law School, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Library, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Materials Support (W. Haas), 1977 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center Advisory Committee (of the Board of Trustees Exec. Comm.), 1973-1974 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center Advisory Committee (of the Board of Trustees Exec. Comm.) 1975-1977 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center -- Controller (Summers), 1967-1977 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center -- Director (Anlyan, CEO), 1977 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital -- Financial Reports, 1978 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital North, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center -- Health Affairs Administration, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center -- Medicare Guidelines, 1976-1977 (Box 34)
  - Medical Center -- Private Diagnostic Clinics (Box 34)
    Private Diagnostic Clinics materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Medical Center -- Parking Garage, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Medicine, Dept. of, 1977 (Box 34)
  - Music Dept., 1974-1977 (Box 34)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO), 1977 (Box 35)
  - North Carolina National Bank (NCNB), 1966-1977 (Box 35)
  - Nursing, School of (Box 35)
  - Organizational Planning, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Payroll -- Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 35)
  - Payroll Revision, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co., 1977 (Box 35)
  - Personnel (Jackson), 1977 (Box 35)
  - Personnel, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Personnel -- Employee Relations, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Personnel -- Labor Relations, 1976-1977 (Box 35)
  - Personnel -- Wage and Salary, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Personnel -- Wage and Salary -- Compensation Survey Report, 1978 (Box 35)
  - Personnel -- Wage and Salary Review Committee, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Personnel Policy Committee, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Physical Education, Dept. of, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Physical Plant (Estill, Dir.), 1977 (Box 35)
  - Physical Plant, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Phytotron, 1977-1978 (Box 35)
  - President's Council on Black Affairs, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Public Safety, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Rauch, Henry E. 1977 (Box 35)
  - Raleigh-Durham (RDU) Airport, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Real Estate, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Renovations -- Cameron Indoor Stadium, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Renovations -- Central Campus Housing, 1974-1977 (Box 35)
  - Renovations -- Construction Projects, 1967-1977 (Box 35)
  - Renovations -- Misc., 1967-1977 (Box 35)
  - Renovations -- Music Dept., 1977 (Box 35)
  - Renovations -- New Dorm, 1974-1976 (Box 35)
  - Renovations -- Summer, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Renovations -- University Union, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Research Triangle Foundation, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Research Triangle Institute, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Retirement, 1977 (Box 35)
  - Safety, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Sanford, Terry (President), 1977 (Box 36)
  - Sea Level Hospital, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Student Affairs, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Student Employees, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Summer School, 1967-1977 (Box 36)
  - T. Rowe Price Associates, Inc. -- Reports, Dec. 1976-April 1977 (Box 36)
  - T. Rowe Price Associates, Inc. -- Reports, May 1977 -- Aug. 1977 (Box 36)